Jacqui Fashimpaur

jacquiwithaq@fb.com • jacquifashimpaur.com

I am a driven and creative researcher in the field of Human-Computer Interaction for immersive interfaces. I aim to build novel interactions that are intuitive, low-friction, and confidence-instilling, while codifying what makes them that way.

EDUCATION

Carnegie Mellon University, Pittsburgh PA

May 2020

Degree: Bachelor of Science in Computer Science **Minors:** Media Design, Film and Media Studies

Honors: University Honors, Andrew Carnegie Society Scholar, Phi Beta Kappa Member, QPA 3.95

PUBLICATIONS

Lauren Herckis, Jessica Cao, **Jacqui Fashimpaur**, Anna Henson, Rachel Rodgers, Thomas W. Corbett III, and Jessica Hammer. *Exploring Hybrid Virtual-Physical Homes*. DIS 2020. **Honorable Mention Award (top 5%)** DOI: https://doi.org/10.1145/3357236.3395561

Jacqui Fashimpaur, Kenrick Kin, and Matt Longest. *PinchType: Text Entry for Virtual and Augmented Reality Using Comfortable Thumb to Fingertip Pinches*. CHI EA 2020. DOI: https://doi.org/10.1145/3334480.3382888

EXPERIENCE

Research Software Engineer, Reality Labs Research (Meta)

May 2019 – Present

- Currently on team investigating wrist-based input combined with a contextual Al-powered interface
- Designing and implementing demos and evaluation studies for novel interaction techniques
- Interned with hand-tracking team, developed pinch-based text entry interface for Oculus Rift with Unity (C#)
- Designed and ran user study for the interface, analyzed results and co-authored LBW research paper

Research Assistant, CMU Human-Computer Interaction Institute

May – December 2018

- Developed four prototype virtual reality rooms for the HTC Vive with Unity (C#) and Maya
- Wrote interview questions, conducted interviews, and synthesized results as co-author of research paper
- The project explores the potential for hybrid virtual-physical homes to improve people's lives

Head Teaching Assistant, CMU School of Computer Science

2017-2018, 2019-2020

- One of 20 TAs for the course "Great Theoretical Ideas in Computer Science" (150-250 students each semester)
- Taught weekly classes, held office hours, graded papers, and answered questions online
- Co-Head TA for the 2019-2020 academic year, assigned TA responsibilities and supported professors

PROJECTS

Matt and Emma's Carnival Conundrum (2021) - 2021.teammatehunt.com/

Art/Story Lead and puzzle writer for Teammate Hunt 2021, a week-long online puzzle hunt in which 384 teams participated. Managed team of eight artists and writers to create the plot and visuals for the hunt.

Doodle Bugs (2020) - doodlebugs.art/

Sole developer of an online puzzle game based around an uncooperative drawing tool. Players must discover the "bugs" in the tool and avoid them or use them to their advantage while trying to draw certain images.

SKILLS

VR Development • User Research • Management • Interaction Design • Public Speaking Unity • C# • C++ • Maya • JavaScript • Java • Web Dev • Android Dev • Video Production